Register of the Leopold Labedz papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Correspondence, 1926-1992
  - Robinson, Frances G., 1966 (Box-folder 27: 38)
  - Roddy, 1976 (Box-folder 27: 39)
  - Rodgers, Sheila, 1968 (Box-folder 27: 40)
  - Rodman, Jane, 1973 (Box-folder 27: 41)
  - Rodney, William, 1972 (Box-folder 27: 42)
  - Roger, 1963 (Box-folder 27: 43)
  - Rogers, Rosemarie, 1970 (Box-folder 27: 44)
  - Rogger, Hans, 1972 (Box-folder 27: 45)
  - Romaniecki, Leon, 1971 (Box-folder 27: 46)
  - Roosa, Robert V., 1970 (Box-folder 27: 47)
  - Rorke, John, 1970 (Box-folder 27: 48)
  - Rose, Elizabeth, 1972 (Box-folder 27: 49)
  - Rosenberg, Bruce L., 1977 (Box-folder 27: 50)
  - Rosenfeld, Shalom, 1968 (Box-folder 27: 51)
  - Rosenheim, J. F., 1973 (Box-folder 27: 52)
  - Rosenthal, Harry Kenneth, 1976 (Box-folder 27: 53)
  - Rosenzweig, Robert M., 1971-1975 (Box-folder 27: 54)
  - Roser, Hal, 1977 (Box-folder 27: 55)
  - Ross, A. I., 1970 (Box-folder 27: 56)
  - Rostow, Eugene V., 1977-1978 (Box-folder 27: 57)
  - Roszek, J. S., 1956, 1958 (Box-folder 27: 58)
  - Roth, S. J., 1958-1986 (Box-folder 27: 59)
  - Rothberg, Abraham, 1971 (Box-folder 27: 60)
  - Rouai, G., 1968-1969 (Box-folder 27: 61)
  - Roucek, Joseph S., 1962 (Box-folder 27: 62)
  - Rousham, Sally, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 27: 63)
  - Rovan, Joseph, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 27: 64)
  - Rowe, Alice J., 1960 (Box-folder 27: 65)
  - Rowny, Edward L., 1979 (Box-folder 27: 66)
  - Rozek, Edward J., 1982-1989 (Box-folder 27: 67)
  - Rozenbaum, Wlodzimierz, 1976 (Box-folder 27: 68)
  - Ruadrelli, Rooloefo, 1973 (Box-folder 27: 69)
  - Rubenstein, Joshua, 1977 (Box-folder 28: 1)
  - Rubin, F., 1972-1974 (Box-folder 28: 2)
  - Ruddy, undated (Box-folder 28: 3)
  - Rudnytsky, Ivan L., 1962 (Box-folder 28: 4)
  - Rudzki, Adam, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 28: 5)
  - Ruggles, Rudy, 1976 (Box-folder 28: 6)
  - Rühle, Jürgen, 1961 (Box-folder 28: 7)
  - Rundle, C. J. S., 1966-1967 (Box-folder 28: 8)
  - Rush, N., 1972 (Box-folder 28: 9)
  - Ruskin, Marc, 1977 (Box-folder 28: 10)
  - Russak, Ben, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 28: 11)
  - de Russy, Candace U., 1985 (Box-folder 28: 12)
  - Rutka and Rysxard, 1972 (Box-folder 28: 13)
  - Ryan, Kenneth, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 28: 14)
  - Ryavec, Karl W., 1969-1971 (Box-folder 28: 15)
  - Ryser, Robert Scott, 1985 (Box-folder 28: 16)
  - Ryser, Witold, 1971 (Box-folder 28: 17)
  - Rywlein, Michael, 1963 (Box-folder 28: 18)
  - R - general, 1957-1985 (Box-folder 28: 19)
  - Sabatani, Angelo, 1969 (Box-folder 28: 20)
  - Salazar, Gonzales, 1970 (Box-folder 28: 21)
  - Sampson, Anthony, 1970 (Box-folder 28: 22)
  - Sanchez-Gijon, Antonio, 1982 (Box-folder 28: 23)
  - Sanders, Richard, 1976 (Box-folder 28: 24)
  - de Santayana, Jesus Pardo, 1977 (Box-folder 28: 25)
  - Sartori, Giovanni, 1971-1981 (Box-folder 28: 26)
  - Sasha, undated (Box-folder 28: 27)
  - Saur, K. G., 1979 (Box-folder 28: 28)
  - Sauzey, François, 1977 (Box-folder 28: 29)
  - Sawczuk, Marta, 1973 (Box-folder 28: 30)
  - Scalapino, Robert, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 28: 31)
  - Scammell, Michael, 1970-1978 (Box-folder 28: 32)
  - Scassellati, Ubaldo, 1971 (Box-folder 28: 33)
  - Schakovskoy, Zinaida, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 28: 34)
  - Schapiro, Leonard, 1959-1980 (Box-folder 28: 35)
  - Schemmer, Benajmin F., 1974 (Box-folder 28: 36)
  - Scherrer, Jutta, 1979 (Box-folder 28: 37)
  - Schiffrin, Harold Z., 1972-1973 (Box-folder 28: 38)
  - Schilling, Hannelore, 1972 (Box-folder 28: 39)
  - Schlacks, Charles, 1972 (Box-folder 28: 40)
  - Schleimann, Jorgen, 1967 (Box-folder 28: 41)
  - Schlesinger, R., 1958 (Box-folder 28: 42)
  - Schmidt, Betsy, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 28: 43)
  - Schneider, Ruth M., 1973-1974 (Box-folder 28: 44)
  - Schneiderman, Jeremiah, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 28: 45)
  - Schopflin, George, 1979, 1985 (Box-folder 28: 46)
  - Schrepfer, Margot, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 28: 47)
  - Schreter, S. M., 1975 (Box-folder 28: 48)
  - Schroeter, Leonard W., 1974 (Box-folder 28: 49)
  - Schultheiss, Thomas, 1972 (Box-folder 28: 50)
  - Schurmann, H. F., 1960 (Box-folder 28: 51)
  - Schwartz, Morton, 1970 (Box-folder 28: 52)
  - Schwarz, Solomon M., 1957-1967 (Box-folder 28: 53)
  - Scrivener, R. S., 1974 (Box-folder 28: 54)
  - Scully, Michael A., 1986 (Box-folder 28: 55)
  - Seabury, Paul, 1972 (Box-folder 28: 56)
  - Secker and Warburg, 1969 (Box-folder 28: 57)
  - Seeger, Murray, 1979 (Box-folder 28: 58)
  - Segal, Gerald, 1970, 1973 (Box-folder 28: 59)
  - Segretti, 1970 (Box-folder 28: 60)
  - Seidensticker, E. G., 1972 (Box-folder 28: 61)
  - Seki, Yoshihiko, 1962-1973 (Box-folder 28: 62)
  - Sellekaerts, Willy, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 28: 63)
  - Seltzer, L. R., 1969 (Box-folder 28: 64)
  - Senft, Paul, 1973 (Box-folder 28: 65)
  - Sergei, 1963 (Box-folder 28: 66)
  - Sesotto, Chi, 1963 (Box-folder 28: 67)
  - Seth, S. P., 1978 (Box-folder 28: 68)
  - Settembrini, Domenico, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 28: 69)
  - Sevray, Susan, 1970 (Box-folder 28: 70)
  - Seymour, Jack Murray, Jr., 1977-1978 (Box-folder 28: 71)
  - Shachtman, Max, 1970-1977 (Box-folder 28: 72)
  - Shaffer, Harry G., 1970-1982 (Box-folder 28: 73)
  - Shah, A. B., 1970-1977 (Box-folder 28: 74)
  - Shakhnovich, Henry, 1976 (Box-folder 28: 75)
  - Shanker, Al, 1975 (Box-folder 28: 76)
  - Shapiro, Harvey, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 28: 77)
  - Sharp, Samuel L., 1962 (Box-folder 28: 78)
  - Shashar, E., 1976 (Box-folder 28: 79)
  - Shattan, Joe, 1986 (Box-folder 29: 1)
  - Shatz, Marshall, 1972 (Box-folder 29: 2)
  - Shawcross, William, Lord, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 29: 3)
  - Sheila, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 29: 4)
  - Shein, L. J., 1972 (Box-folder 29: 5)
  - Shenitzer, Sarah, 1975 (Box-folder 29: 6)
  - Shenker, A., 1971-1976 (Box-folder 29: 7)
  - Sherman, Alfred, 1962 (Box-folder 29: 8)
  - Shils, Edward, 1964-1986 (Box-folder 29: 9)
  - Shlaim, Avi, 1972 (Box-folder 29: 10)
  - Shlapentokh, Vladimir, 1986 (Box-folder 29: 11)
  - Shonfield, Andrew, 1970-1979 (Box-folder 29: 12)
  - Shub, Joyce, 1976-1982 (Box-folder 29: 13)
  - Shub, Tony, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 29: 14)
  - Shuchman, Harry, 1977 (Box-folder 29: 15)
  - Shukman, Harold, 1971 (Box-folder 29: 16)
  - Shulman, Marshall D., 1960-1974 (Box-folder 29: 17)
  - Siani, Harriette, 1973 (Box-folder 29: 18)
  - Sidorsky, David, 1985 (Box-folder 29: 19)
  - Siegelman, Philip, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 29: 20)
  - Sierotwinska, Muzia, 1982 (Box-folder 29: 21)
  - Sijthoff, A. W., 1968-1970 (Box-folder 29: 22)
  - Sikorski, Radosław, 1985 (Box-folder 29: 23)
  - Silone, Ignazio, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 29: 24)
  - Simes, Dimitri K., 1977-1978 (Box-folder 29: 25)
  - Simirenko, Alex, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 29: 26)
  - Simmons, Ernest J., 1962 (Box-folder 29: 27)
  - Singer, Aubrey, 1968 (Box-folder 29: 28)
  - Sionil, Jose F., 1968 (Box-folder 29: 29)
  - Sirc, L., 1962 (Box-folder 29: 30)
  - Sirovich, Chrislana, 1968 (Box-folder 29: 31)
  - Skolimowski, Henryk, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 29: 32)
  - Skolimowski, Wojciech, 1985 (Box-folder 29: 33)
  - Slaiman, Donald, 1978 (Box-folder 29: 34)
  - Slater, John, 1977 (Box-folder 29: 35)
  - Sleiter, Romelle, 1972 (Box-folder 29: 36)
  - Slonim, Marc, 1966 (Box-folder 29: 37)
  - Smith, Charles, 1977 (Box-folder 29: 38)
  - Smith, Gerard, 1974 (Box-folder 29: 39)
  - Smith, John H., 1963 (Box-folder 29: 40)
  - Smith, Paul A., 1971-1977 (Box-folder 29: 41)
  - Smith, Rachel, 1965 (Box-folder 29: 42)
  - Smith, Steve, 1986 (Box-folder 29: 43)
  - Smolar, Aleksander, 1974 (Box-folder 29: 44)
  - Smolar, Eugeniusz, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 29: 45)
  - Smolinski, Leon, 1973 (Box-folder 29: 46)
  - Snell, C., 1978 (Box-folder 29: 47)
  - Snikere, Velta, 1970 (Box-folder 29: 48)
  - Soderland, Dorothy, 1967 (Box-folder 29: 49)
  - Soedjatmoko, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 29: 50)
  - Solchanyk, Roman, 1976 (Box-folder 29: 51)
  - Solecki, J., 1973 (Box-folder 29: 52)
  - Solomon, Susan G., 1971 (Box-folder 29: 53)
  - Solski, Wacław, 1973-1978 (Box-folder 29: 54)
  - Solzhenitsyn, Alexander I., 1971-1986 (Box-folder 29: 55)
  - Solzhenitsyn, Natalia, 1986 (Box-folder 29: 56)
  - Sommer, Theo, Dr., 1973 (Box-folder 29: 57)
  - Sondhi, Shrimati Madhuri, 1969 (Box-folder 29: 58)
  - Sonnenfeldt, Helmut, 1962 (Box-folder 29: 59)
  - Sorenson, Jay B., 1963 (Box-folder 29: 60)
  - Sormani, Pietro, 1970-1978 (Box-folder 29: 61)
  - Sosin, Gene, 1973 (Box-folder 29: 62)
  - Soutou, Jean-Marie, undated (Box-folder 29: 63)
  - Souvarine, Boris, 1969-1981 (Box-folder 29: 64)
  - Spaeth, Carl, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 29: 65)
  - Sperber, Manes, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 29: 66)
  - Spiegel, Steven L., 1986 (Box-folder 29: 67)
  - Spitz, David, 1974 (Box-folder 29: 68)
  - Staar, Richard F., 1973 (Box-folder 29: 69)
  - Staats, Steven, 1971 (Box-folder 29: 70)
  - Staehle, R. W., 1977-1978 (Box-folder 30: 1)
  - Staffa, Dario, 1969-1977 (Box-folder 30: 2)
  - Stahle, Nils, circa 1971 (Box-folder 30: 3)
  - Stallybrass, Oliver, 1976 (Box-folder 30: 4)
  - Stanford, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 30: 5-6)
  - Stankiewicz, Marketa Goetz, Dr., 1978-1979 (Box-folder 30: 7)
  - Stansky, Peter, 1973 (Box-folder 30: 8)
  - Starobin, Joseph R., 1970 (Box-folder 30: 9)
  - Stent, Angela, 1973 (Box-folder 30: 10)
  - Sternberg, Hilary, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 30: 11)
  - Stevens, R. Hilary, 1960 (Box-folder 30: 12)
  - Stirling, Irene, 1967 (Box-folder 30: 13)
  - Stone, Shepard, 1967-1979 (Box-folder 30: 14)
  - Stoppard, Tom, 1977 (Box-folder 30: 15)
  - Strategic Studies Center, 1974 (Box-folder 30: 16)
  - Struve, Gleb, 1974 (Box-folder 30: 17)
  - Studi, Ufficio, 1972 (Box-folder 30: 18)
  - Stypulkowski, Andrew, 1972-1979 (Box-folder 30: 19)
  - Subrahmanyam, K., 1974 (Box-folder 30: 20)
  - Sue and Lionel, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 30: 21)
  - Sullock, Alan, 1974 (Box-folder 30: 22)
  - Suny, Ronald Grigor, 1979 (Box-folder 30: 23)
  - Surażska, Wiesława, 1986 (Box-folder 30: 24)
  - Surkov, Alexei, 1966 (Box-folder 30: 25)
  - Survey Bulletin subscriptions, 1961-1973 (Box-folder 30: 26)
  - Sussman, Leonard, 1975-1981 (Box-folder 30: 27)
  - Svirsky, Grigori, 1972 (Box-folder 31: 1)
  - Sworakowski, Witold, 1973 (Box-folder 31: 2)
  - Szafar, Tadeusz, 1978 (Box-folder 31: 3)
  - Szajkowski, Bogdan, 1970 (Box-folder 31: 4)
  - Szamuely, Tibor, 1972 (Box-folder 31: 5)
  - Szanuely, Nina, 1973 (Box-folder 31: 6)
  - Szirmai-Sebestyen, M., 1973 (Box-folder 31: 7)
  - S - general, 1966-1977 (Box-folder 31: 8)
  - Taborski, B., 1962 (Box-folder 31: 9)
  - Taeuber, Conrad, 1962 (Box-folder 31: 10)
  - Tambs, Lewis A., undated (Box-folder 31: 11)
  - Tames, Richard, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 31: 12)
  - Tanaka, Naokichi, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 31: 13)
  - Tatu, Michel, 1970 (Box-folder 31: 14)
  - Taylor, Allen, 1980 (Box-folder 31: 15)
  - Taylor, Marilyn, 1971 (Box-folder 31: 16)
  - Tellis, Ashley J., 1985 (Box-folder 31: 17)
  - Temple, W. F., 1969 (Box-folder 31: 18)
  - van Thal, Herbert, 1966 (Box-folder 31: 19)
  - Thibaud, Paul, 1967 (Box-folder 31: 20)
  - Thomas, C., 1979 (Box-folder 31: 21)
  - Thomas, Hugh, 1978 (Box-folder 31: 22)
  - Thomas, John R., 1971-1977 (Box-folder 31: 23)
  - Thomas, Patricia, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 31: 24)
  - Thomas, Susan L., 1968 (Box-folder 31: 25)
  - Thomson, Ralph J., 1972 (Box-folder 31: 26)
  - Thorton, Lesley, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 31: 27)
  - Thumm, G. W., 1969 (Box-folder 31: 28)
  - Tibenham, 1978 (Box-folder 31: 29)
  - Tieter, Jerry, 1963 (Box-folder 31: 30)
  - Tigrid, Pavel, 1962, 1972 (Box-folder 31: 31)
  - Tilliun, G., 1973 (Box-folder 31: 32)
  - Timofejeff, A., 1975 (Box-folder 31: 33)
  - Tobak, Martha, 1981 (Box-folder 31: 34)
  - Tochitch, Desimir, 1966-1971 (Box-folder 31: 35)
  - Togo, Takehiro, 1970, 1977 (Box-folder 31: 36)
  - Tökés, Rudolf L., 1975 (Box-folder 31: 37)
  - Tolek, 1962 (Box-folder 31: 38)
  - Tonska, A., 1971 (Box-folder 31: 39)
  - Toth, János, 1968 (Box-folder 31: 40)
  - Towle, Philip, 1982 (Box-folder 31: 41)
  - Toyne, Anthony, 1974-1982 (Box-folder 31: 42)
  - Trambley, Stephen, 1986 (Box-folder 31: 43)
  - Treadgold, Donald W., 1970-1974 (Box-folder 31: 44)
  - Treavor-Roper, Hugh, 1971, 1976 (Box-folder 31: 45)
  - Trilling, Lionel, undated (Box-folder 31: 46)
  - Tucker, H. H., 1969 (Box-folder 31: 47)
  - Tucker, Robert C., 1971 (Box-folder 31: 48)
  - Turzyńska, Maria, 1986 (Box-folder 31: 49)
  - Tütsch, Hans E., 1962 (Box-folder 31: 50)
  - Twierdochlebow, W., 1980 (Box-folder 31: 51)
  - Twiselton, Ann, 1986 (Box-folder 31: 52)
  - Tyrmand, Leopold, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 31: 53)
  - T - general, 1956-1974 (Box-folder 31: 54)
  - Ulam, Adam B., 1960-1982 (Box-folder 31: 55)
  - Ulmen, G. L., 1982 (Box-folder 31: 56)
  - Unger, Leopold, 1971-1980 (Box-folder 31: 57)
  - Unwin, Rayner, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 31: 58)
  - Unwin, Stanley, 1961 (Box-folder 31: 59)
  - Urban, Geroge, 1962-1976 (Box-folder 31: 60)
  - Urbanowski, Frank, 1976 (Box-folder 31: 61)
  - Ussachevsky, Vladimir A., 1962 (Box-folder 31: 62)
  - Utechin, Pat, 1973, 1977 (Box-folder 31: 63)
  - Uysal, Kadir, 1971 (Box-folder 31: 64)
  - U - general, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 31: 65)
  - Valenta, Jiri, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 31: 66)
  - Valkenier, Elizabeth K., 1970-1973 (Box-folder 31: 67)
  - Vangeen, Peter I., 1969 (Box-folder 31: 68)
  - Vardys, Stanley, 1981 (Box-folder 31: 69)
  - Vaughn, Michalina, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 31: 70)
  - Vega, Luis Mercier, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 31: 71)
  - Velen, Victor A., 1970-1986 (Box-folder 31: 72)
  - Venturi, Franco, 1970 (Box-folder 32: 1)
  - Victor, 1969 (Box-folder 32: 2)
  - Villeneuve, B., undated (Box-folder 32: 3)
  - Villiers, Marjorie, 1971-1977 (Box-folder 32: 4)
  - Viney, Deryck E., 1969, 1978 (Box-folder 32: 5)
  - Vlachoutsicos, Charalambos, 1986 (Box-folder 32: 6)
  - Vladeck, Stephen C., 1977 (Box-folder 32: 7)
  - Voinovich, Vladimir, 1985 (Box-folder 32: 8)
  - Volle, Hermann, 1967 (Box-folder 32: 9)
  - Vondracek, Th. J., 1973 (Box-folder 32: 10)
  - van Voren, Robert, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 32: 11)
  - Vrabec, Sylvia B., 1980 (Box-folder 32: 12)
  - Vrga, Djuro J., 1970-1971 (Box-folder 32: 13)
  - V - general, 1967-1973 (Box-folder 32: 14)
  - Wade, William W., 1977 (Box-folder 32: 15)
  - Wagman, Donald, 1974 (Box-folder 32: 16)
  - Wain, John, 1973 (Box-folder 32: 17)
  - Waldman, Guido P., 1978 (Box-folder 32: 18)
  - Walker, Richard, 1970 (Box-folder 32: 19)
  - Walkin, Jacob, 1970, 1976 (Box-folder 32: 20)
  - Wall, Bernard, 1966 (Box-folder 32: 21)
  - Wallerstein, 1963 (Box-folder 32: 22)
  - Wallis, Peter, 1970 (Box-folder 32: 23)
  - Walmsley, Margot, 1978 (Box-folder 32: 24)
  - Walter, undated (Box-folder 32: 25)
  - Wane, M., 1928, 1968 (Box-folder 32: 26)
  - Wapler, 1971 (Box-folder 32: 27)
  - Warner, Malcolm, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 32: 28)
  - Warren, Richard, 1976 (Box-folder 32: 29)
  - Wasowski, Stanislaw, 1973 (Box-folder 32: 30)
  - Wat, Paulina, 1962-1974 (Box-folder 32: 31)
  - Watson, Adam, 1974-1981 (Box-folder 32: 32)
  - Watson, George, 1973 (Box-folder 32: 33)
  - Weaamann, E., 1956 (Box-folder 32: 34)
  - Webb, Nola, 1958 (Box-folder 32: 35)
  - Webb, W., 1969 (Box-folder 32: 36)
  - Webber, Eric, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 32: 37)
  - Weber, Eckhard, 1972 (Box-folder 32: 38)
  - Webster, David, 1968 (Box-folder 32: 39)
  - Webster, John, 1968 (Box-folder 32: 40)
  - Weeks, Albert L., 1982 (Box-folder 32: 41)
  - Weightwen, John, 1970 (Box-folder 32: 42)
  - Weil, Boris, 1980 (Box-folder 32: 43)
  - Wensberg, Erik, 1960 (Box-folder 32: 44)
  - Wesson, Robert, 1974-1979 (Box-folder 32: 45)
  - Westoby, Adam, 1985 (Box-folder 32: 46)
  - Westowski, W., 1959 (Box-folder 32: 47)
  - Wetter, Gustav A., 1976 (Box-folder 32: 48)
  - Wheeler, Marcus, 1970 (Box-folder 32: 49)
  - Whelan, Joseph G., 1971 (Box-folder 32: 50)
  - Wheldon, Huw, Sir, undated (Box-folder 32: 51)
  - Whetton, Lawrence L., 1971 (Box-folder 32: 52)
  - Whitby, Anthony, 1968 (Box-folder 32: 53)
  - Whitcomb, John, 1968, 1976 (Box-folder 32: 54)
  - Whitney, Ray, 1980 (Box-folder 32: 55)
  - Whyte, Martin, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 32: 56)
  - Widmayer, Ruth, 1968 (Box-folder 32: 57)
  - Wierski, R., 1973 (Box-folder 32: 58)
  - Wierzbicki, Piotr, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 32: 59)
  - Wieseltier, Leon, 1985 (Box-folder 32: 60)
  - Wiesenthal, Simon, 1975 (Box-folder 32: 61)
  - Wilder, Emilia, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 32: 62)
  - Wiles, Peter, 1957-1979 (Box-folder 32: 63)
  - Wilk, H., 1976 (Box-folder 32: 64)
  - Wilkins, John, 1967 (Box-folder 32: 65)
  - Will, George F., 1980-1989 (Box-folder 32: 66)
  - Willetts, Harry, 1965-1968 (Box-folder 32: 67)
  - Wilson, David C., 1973 (Box-folder 32: 68)
  - Wilson, Edmund, 1972 (Box-folder 32: 69)
  - Wilson, J. L. J., 1957 (Box-folder 33: 1)
  - Winter, Charles, 1968 (Box-folder 33: 2)
  - Wirth, Andrzej, 1972 (Box-folder 33: 3)
  - Wistrich, Robert S., 1975 (Box-folder 33: 4)
  - Witzenfeld, John, 1965 (Box-folder 33: 5)
  - Włodarczyk, Wojciech, 1976 (Box-folder 33: 6)
  - Wohl, Paul, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 33: 7)
  - Wohlstetter, Albert, 1974-1980 (Box-folder 33: 8)
  - Wolbers, H. L., 1973 (Box-folder 33: 9)
  - Wolfe, Bertram D., 1962-1976 (Box-folder 33: 10)
    See also: Box 13, Folder 24.
  - Wolfe, Ella, 1978-1985 (Box-folder 33: 11)
  - Wolfe, Thomas W., 1968 (Box-folder 33: 12)
  - Wolfenden, Sheilia, 1971-1979 (Box-folder 33: 13)
  - Wolferen, K. G., 1979-1980 (Box-folder 33: 14)
  - Wolff, Kurt H., 1961 (Box-folder 33: 15)
  - Wolff, Lester, 1976 (Box-folder 33: 16)
  - Wolfsohn, H., 1957 (Box-folder 33: 17)
  - Woolley, Geofrey, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 33: 18)
  - Wordemann, Franz, 1962 (Box-folder 33: 19)
  - Worthington, Peter, 1969-1975 (Box-folder 33: 20)
  - Wright, James, 1973 (Box-folder 33: 21)
  - Wurmbrand, Michael, 1970 (Box-folder 33: 22)
  - Wuxmasic, Jonathan and Jolanta, 1988 (Box-folder 33: 23)
  - Wydra, Denise J., 1982 (Box-folder 33: 24)
  - Wynot, Edward D., 1970 (Box-folder 33: 25)
  - W - general, 1970-1979 (Box-folder 33: 26)
  - Yadfat, Aryeh, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 33: 27)
  - Yager, Susanna, 1969 (Box-folder 33: 28)
  - Yakobson, Sergius, Dr., 1973 (Box-folder 33: 29)
  - Yakolevich, Leopold, 1974 (Box-folder 33: 30)
  - Yakvshev, A., undated (Box-folder 33: 31)
  - Yedlin, T., 1982 (Box-folder 33: 32)
  - Yntema, Esther S., 1960 (Box-folder 33: 33)
  - Yoakum, Robert N., 1965 (Box-folder 33: 34)
  - Young, James, 1969-1977 (Box-folder 33: 35)
  - Young, Peter, 1982 (Box-folder 33: 36)
  - Yule, David, 1977 (Box-folder 33: 37)
  - Zaleski, Eugene, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 33: 38)
  - Zamojska, Hilline, 1967 (Box-folder 33: 39)
  - Zamowska, Teresa and Stefan, undated (Box-folder 33: 40)
  - Zamoyski, A., 1960 (Box-folder 33: 41)
  - Zanker, Roman, 1963 (Box-folder 33: 42)
  - Zarzewski, St., 1970 (Box-folder 33: 43)
  - Zauberman, Alfred, 1972 (Box-folder 33: 44)
  - Zawodny, J. K., 1969, 1979 (Box-folder 33: 45)
  - Zdziechowski, K., 1975-1976 (Box-folder 33: 46)
  - Zelter, M., Dr., 1979 (Box-folder 33: 47)
  - Zeman, Z. A. B., 1961, 1978 (Box-folder 33: 48)
  - Zend, Robert, 1972 (Box-folder 33: 49)
  - Zielinkski, Janusz, 1970 (Box-folder 33: 50)
  - Zinam, Oleg, 1971 (Box-folder 33: 51)
  - Zink, Karl, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 33: 52)
  - Zinner, Paul E., 1969 (Box-folder 33: 53)
  - Zogona, Don, 1967 (Box-folder 33: 54)
  - Zoppo, Ciro, 1973 (Box-folder 33: 55)
  - Zorza, Victor, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 33: 56)
  - Zucker, J. W., 1960 (Box-folder 33: 57)
  - Zumwalt, E. R., Jr., 1976 (Box-folder 33: 58)
  - Zur, S., 1972 (Box-folder 33: 59)
  - Zuta, Julian, 1976 (Box-folder 33: 60)
  - Zuzowski, Robert, 1986 (Box-folder 33: 61)
  - Unidentified, 1958-1978 (Box-folder 33: 62)
- Congress for Cultural Freedom (CCF) / International Association for Cultural Freedom (IACF) File, 1956-1977
  Documents pertaining to the history and activities of the CCF/IACF. Additional materials document the organization’s relationship with Survey.
  - Activities of the CCF, 1972-1977 (Box-folder 34: 1)
  - Background and organization, 1962-1969 (Box-folder 34: 2)
  - Biographies, undated (Box-folder 34: 3)
  - Budgets, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 34: 4)
  - Committee for the Free World, undated (Box-folder 34: 5)
  - IACF in Paris - general, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 34: 6)
  - Library of International Studies, interim report, 1962 (Box-folder 34: 7)
  - Magazines published or co-sponsored by IACF, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 34: 8)
  - Newsletters, 1956-1968 (Box-folder 34: 9)
  - Press releases, 1967 (Box-folder 34: 10)
  - Quarterly financial reports, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 34: 11)
  - Reorganization of the CCF, 1967 September 16 (Box-folder 34: 12)
  - Trahisen des Clercs, 1963 (Box-folder 34: 13)
  - Writings, 1960-1967 (Box-folder 34: 14)
- Conferences File, 1954-1987
  Materials on conferences, seminars, and symposiums attended by Labedz. When possible, Labedz's original order was maintained.
  - Alumni Association of the City College of New York, 1961 (Box-folder 34: 15)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Slavic Studies, 1963-1985 (Box-folder 34: 16-17)
  - American Council of Learned Societies; Research Conference on Communist Revolution, 1973 (Box-folder 35: 1)
  - American Political Science Association, 1970 (Box-folder 35: 2)
  - American Sociological Association, 1962 (Box-folder 35: 3)
  - Amnesty International, 1961-1968 (Box-folder 35: 4)
  - Annual World Conference of Journalists, 1977 (Box-folder 35: 5)
  - Arms Control and Foreign Policy, 1974 (Box-folder 35: 6)
  - BANF International Conference, 1974 (Box-folder 35: 7)
  - Bonn Conference, 1980 (Box-folder 35: 8)
  - The British Sociological Association, 1958-1985 (Box-folder 35: 9)
  - Brighton Conference, 1972 (Box-folder 35: 10)
  - Carleton University, 1986 (Box-folder 35: 11)
  - CAUSA (Confederation of the Associations for the Unification of the Societies of the Americas), 1985 (Box-folder 35: 12)
  - Central and East European Commission, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 35: 13)
  - Chinese Communist Historiography, 1964 (Box-folder 35: 14-15, 36: 1-3)
  - Columbia University: Russian Institute, 1962-1978 (Box-folder 36: 4)
  - Columbia University: Research Institute on International Change, 1975 (Box-folder 36: 5-6, 37: 1)
  - Conference of Communist Parties of the Capitalist Countries in Europe, 1974 (Box-folder 37: 2)
  - Conference on Neutralism, 1961 (Box-folder 37: 3)
  - Congress for Cultural Freedom (CCF) / International Association for Cultural Freedom (IACF), 1960-1972
    Comprised of conferences sponsored by CCF/IACF. When possible, Labedz's original order was maintained.
    - Aspen, Colorado, 1970 (Box-folder 37: 4)
    - "The Crisis of the Industrial Civilization,", 1970 (Box-folder 37: 5)
    - "Cultural Diversity and Post-Industrial Society,", 1970 (Box-folder 37: 6)
    - General Conference in Berlin, 1960 (Box-folder 37: 7)
    - General Conferences, 1960 (Box-folder 37: 8)
    - Geneva Conference correspondence, 1962 (Box-folder 37: 9-10)
    - "The Historian Between the Ethnologist and Futurologist,", 1971 (Box-folder 38: 1)
    - "L'Imagination Créative,", 1970 (Box-folder 38: 2)
    - "Pacifism and Violence - Their Uses and Limitations as Instruments of Reform,", 1969 (Box-folder 38: 3)
    - "Post Industrial Society and Cultural Diversity,", 1970 (Box-folder 38: 4)
    - "The Relevance of History,", 1970 (Box-folder 38: 5)
    - "The Role and Responsibility of Intellectuals in Contemporary Society,", 1972 (Box-folder 38: 6)
    - "The Socialist Idea,", 1970 (Box-folder 38: 7)
    - "Standards of Information and Independence of the Press,", 1970-1972 (Box-folder 38: 8)
    - "Technology and Science - Social Control and Cultural Implications,", 1969-1970 (Box-folder 38: 9)
    - "L'unité de l'homme,", 1972 (Box-folder 38: 10)
    - "The United States, Its Problems, Impact and Image in the World,", 1968 (Box-folder 38: 11)
  - Council of Europe, 1971-1987 (Box-folder 38: 12)
  - Council on Free Czechoslovakia, 1977 (Box-folder 38: 13)